I cannot believe that you didn't tell me we are still married!
你居然沒告訴我 我們還是夫妻
Look,I was going to tell you.
我有打算告訴你
When? After the birth of our first secret child?
什麼時候？ 第一個小孩偷偷出生後？
Ross didn't get the annulment. We are still married!
羅斯沒辦註銷，我們還是夫妻
-You're kidding. -Oh,my God!
什麼？ 我的天哪
It wasn't my best decision,but I couldn't face another failed marriage.
或許這個決定不好 但我無法面對另一次失敗婚姻
At what point did you think this was a successful marriage?
我插個嘴 你覺得這段婚姻哪裡成功？
Rach,come on. If you think about it, it's actually kind of funny.
別這樣，其實想想還蠻好笑的
Maybe it's best not to think about it.
還是不要想好了
This is inexcusable. I'm shocked to my very core.
這真是不可原諒 我真是震驚到了極點
Phoebe,I told her you already knew.
菲比，我已經說你知道了
Another lie. You have a sickness!
又在騙人，你真的有病
For my own peace of mind, are you married to any more of us?
羅斯，你沒娶我們其他人吧？
Look,Rach,I was going to tell you.
我有打算要告訴你
I just wanted to do it in my own way.
我只是想用我的方式說
Yes,silently,with no words.
是啊，無聲勝有聲的方式
Look,in Ross' defense,okay....
我要替羅斯說句話…
The One With Joey's Porsche
本集播出：「名車狂想曲」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Someone left their keys.
有人掉了鑰匙…
To a Porsche.
是保時捷
-Are these yours? -Yeah. That's what I drive.
阿甘，這是你的嗎？ 是啊，我開保時捷
I make 4 bucks an hour. I saved up for 350 years.
我時薪4塊錢，存了350年
少來了
Did anybody lose their keys?
有人掉了鑰匙嗎？
Put them in the lost and found.
你可以放進失物招領箱
There's a lost and found?
這裡有失物招領箱？
My shoe!
我的鞋子
You left a shoe here?
你掉了一隻鞋在這裡？
I didn't realize till I got home. I wasn't gonna walk back with one shoe.
我回到家才發現 我才不要光著一隻腳再回來
I'll go find that guy's car and leave a note on the windshield.
我要去找那輛車，然後留言
When he comes back for his keys, I'll give him your shoe.
等他來了我會把你的鞋子給他
Great. Thanks.
太好了，謝謝
Oh,good. You guys are here. Listen.
太好了，你們在這裡
How would you like to spend tomorrow taking care of three cute puppies?
明天要不要一起照顧 三隻超可愛的小狗？
My God! What a fun day! Sounds great!
好棒喔，聽起來好好玩
Yeah,all right.
好吧
I'll bring them by tomorrow morning.
好，我明早帶他們過來
By the way,they're not actually puppies.
對了，其實不是小狗
They're Frank and Alice's triplets. See you.
是法蘭克的三胞胎，好，再見
What?
什麼？
Please,please,please? Frank and Alice...
拜託拜託拜託…
asked me to baby-sit them. I'm nervous. I've never done that.
他們托我帶小孩，我好緊張 我沒有一個人帶過小孩
Don't worry. We'll do it.
放心，我們一定會幫忙
I'm gonna pass,because I was kind of iffy when it was puppies.
我就不了 是狗狗時我就很猶豫了
Come on,Chandler. It'll give us great practice for when...
好啦，這是練習的好機會…
people with babies come to visit.
總會有客人帶小孩來
不是那輛
So I still have boxes here.
這裡還有我的東西
I still have boxes at Ross'.
羅斯家也有我的東西
And I have nowhere to live.
而我卻沒地方住
I could so easily freak out right now.
我現在應該要捉狂才對
What about me? Denise is leaving town for a while. I don't have a roommate.
那我呢？我剛發現 狄妮絲要出遠門，我沒室友了
Well,maybe I could be your roommate,Phoebe.
也許我可以當你的室友
Maybe you could be my roommate!
也對
Well,there's an idea!
有辦法了 沒錯
That would be great!
太好了！
-How long is Denise gone for? -She said she'd be back December 26th.
狄妮絲要去多久？ 她說她12月26日回來
December 26th.
12月26日
Maybe she's Santa Claus.
也許她是聖誕老公公
Oh,look who it is. My husband,the apple of my eye.
看，是我老公，我的心肝寶貝
Okay,I got us a court date for tomorrow at 2...
我已經約好明天2點出庭
and I picked up all the forms.
表格也都拿了
I'll take care of it.
我會搞定
Sure,if you say you'll take care of it,I have no reason to doubt you.
當然，既然你說你會搞定 我當然沒理由懷疑你
Give me those forms.
拿來啦
I'm gonna do this my way and I don't wanna hear a peep out of you.
我要照我的方式去做 你不准嘰嘰歪歪
-Okay, Rach,but.. -You're peeping!
好，但是… 你在嘰嘰歪歪喔
Ross,I just got..
你知道嗎？我實在是…
-Why did you do this? -I told you..
你為什麼要這樣？ 我說過…
I don't wanna hear "three failed marriages."
我不想聽三次失敗的婚姻
If you'd had two failed marriages, you'd understand.
如果你失敗過兩次就會瞭解了
Thanks to you, I'm halfway there.
多虧你，我現在只差一次
Oh,I am so mad,Ross! I don't think I've ever been this angry!
我快氣死了 我從來沒有這麼氣過
What about when I said we were on a break?
我說我們分手了那次呢？
-Nice car. -Yeah,it's not mine.
好車 不是我的
-I love your car. -Yeah,it's mine.
我喜歡你的車 它是…我的
-I bet it's fast. -Me too. Yeah.
一定很能跑 我想也是
And comfortable.
而且很舒服
-You like leather seats? -Yeah.
你喜歡皮椅嗎？ 喜歡
It's got them!
它有皮椅
Phoebe,how's it going?
菲比，你那邊怎樣？
I'm okay. Are they having fun? Am I talking too fast?
還好，蠻不錯的 你覺得他們開心嗎？ 我講話太快了嗎？
No. You sound like me.
不會，跟我差不多
It's going great. Look at Chandler with Little Baby Girl Chandler.
一切都很好 你看錢德和小女生錢德
Little Baby Girl Chandler. Where have I heard that before? Oh,Coach Rubin.
小女生錢德，我在哪裡聽過？ 對了，魯本教練
Phoebe,when you're done over there, we've got a situation over here too.
菲比，等你那邊忙完 我們這裡也有狀況
No. We are all responsible for our own babies.
不行，自己的小孩自己顧
That's where you're wrong. We've been playing them man-to-man.
那你就錯了 我們一直採取人盯人戰術
We should really be playing a zone defense.
但我們應該打區域聯防
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
Things'll go smoother if we each have a zone. Phoebe,be in charge of wiping.
我覺得一人守一區會比較順暢 菲比，你可以負責擦屁屁
Mon,be in charge of diapering.
摩妮卡，你負責包尿布
I'll be in charge of looking at how cute they are when they put their hands...
我就負責看他們捉著我的手…
Sounds great, but you should be in charge of wiping.
好主意，也許你才應該擦屁屁
Okay,I'm a rookie. I should not be in the end zone.
我是菜鳥，不該守球門區
This is so great. This is exactly how we set the plates at the restaurant.
真好，餐廳都這樣準備餐點的
Yeah? Well, this is not what I ordered.
是嗎？我可不是點這個
Hey,guys.
大家好
Hey,babies.
寶寶們好
I'm having the best morning.
早上真過癮
That Porsche I've got the keys to? Still there.
那輛保時捷還在
Shocking, since you still have the keys.
不會吧，畢竟鑰匙在你手上
You should see the treatment I get with that car.
你應該看看大家對我的態度
People are friendly. They wanna talk. And not just about the car.
每個人都很友善，找我聊天 而且不只是聊車子
One guy advised me on my equity investments.
還有人教我投資策略
What equity investments?
什麼投資？
The ones that got me the Porsche. Will you keep up?
賺到保時捷的股票投資 你跟上好嗎？
If people see me just standing there, they're gonna think I don't own it.
但要是我光杵在那裡 別人會覺得那不是我的車
So I figure I'll wash it. Monica, you got a bucket and soap?
所以我要洗車 摩妮卡，你有水桶和肥皂嗎？
Oh,yeah. I got soap and sponges and rags...
有，我有肥皂、海綿、抹布
and carnauba wax and polishing compound.
亮光臘和打臘工具組
You don't even have a car.
你根本沒有車
I know. Once there was a dirty car in front of the building,so I washed it.
對，但樓下停過一輛很髒的車 我就把它給洗了
-And? -And six others.
還有呢？ 還有另外六輛
There you are.
這就對了
Yeah,she tops out at 130.
它可以飆到130
That's just in the city. I get her up to 160 upstate.
這還是市內 到了郊外可以軋到160
Really? You got a place upstate?
是嗎？你在郊外有房子？
Sure.
當然
-All right. See you later. -Okay. Take it easy.
改天見 好，慢走
Hey. That's my car.
喂？那是我的車
Really?
是嗎？
Just give me five more minutes.
再給我5分鐘
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
I found the keys and now I'm just polishing her up.
我檢到鑰匙，現在在幫它打臘
-But it's my car. -Yeah,but it's my wax.
但這是我的車 這是我的臘
Listen,I don't come to the city much.
聽著，我很少進市區
I don't know if you're crazy or if this is some street theater...
我不知道你是瘋子 還是在演街頭劇
but could I have my keys?
但請把鑰匙還給我
Sure. Yeah. I'll save your parking spot.
拿去 我幫你佔車位
I'm not coming back.
我不回來了
-Why not? -I live upstate.
為什麼？ 我住在郊外
Yeah,so did I.
是啊，我本來也是
I don't know why I was so nervous...
我之前不曉得在緊張什麼
and why Frank and Alice complain. This is easy.
法蘭克他們為什麼會抱怨 帶孩子太容易了
Yeah, two hours, a lifetime, that's the same.
是啊，2小時和一輩子一樣
Check it out! When the babies wake up...
你們看 寶寶醒來後
they can meet Krog!
可以認識克洛格
That thing could put someone's eye out.
你在幹什麼？那個東西會害人
He can do more than that. He can destroy the universe.
不只，他還能毀滅宇宙
They could swallow one of those little parts.
不，寶寶可能會誤食那些零件
Also,look at his smooth area. That's just gonna mess them up.
而且那個光滑的部位 會誤導他們
It's just not an appropriate toy for 1-year-olds. Or 30-year-olds.
這種玩具不適合1歲的寶寶 和30歲的男人
They won't swallow anything. You're too overprotective.
他們才不會誤食什麼 你們這叫保護過度
When I was a kid,my mom used to throw me into a pile of broken glass.
我小時候 我媽都把我扔在碎玻璃堆裡
-What? -Glass, sand, whatever.
什麼？ 玻璃，沙子，還不都一樣嘛
Look at little Leslie stretching in her sleep.
小萊絲莉邊睡邊伸懶腰
Oh,it's so cute.
好可愛喔
I wonder when you stop putting both legs behind your head.
不知道要到幾歲 才沒辦法把腿舉到頭上
I can still do that.
我現在還是可以
How are you still single?
你怎麼會還沒結婚？
I thought about it and maybe you're right. Maybe Krog is not a safe toy.
好吧，我想或許你們說得對 或許克洛格不夠安全
-What made you change your mind? -I swallowed his sonic blaster gun.
你為什麼改口了？ 我吞了音波死光槍
How did that happen?
怎麼會這樣？
I was trying to prove that I was right.
我想證明我是對的
And it turns out I was wrong...
結果我錯了
and now it's lodged in my throat.
現在它卡在我的喉嚨裡
This whole time we were concentrating on the babies...
真是的，我們光顧著帶小孩
and no one was watching Chandler!
都忘了要看著錢德
You are asking the court for an annulment?
兩位要申請註銷婚姻？
Yes, Your Honor. Here are our forms, all filled out.
是的，申請表都填好了
So based on your petition...
根據申請書所言
you are seeking an annulment on the grounds...
你申請註銷的理由是
that "Mr. Geller is mentally unstable."
蓋勒先生的精神狀況不穩定
Fine. I'm mentally unstable.
好，我精神狀況不穩定
And based on the fact that "Mr. Geller is an intravenous drug user."
而且他使用靜脈注射毒品
-What? -Yes. Heroin and crack.
什麼？ 是的，海洛因與快克
Crack isn't even an intravenous drug.
快克根本不是靜脈注射毒品
Well,you would know.
你當然瞭解了
Now, it also says here that you...
這上面還說...
"lied about your sexual preference before marriage."
你在婚前隱瞞性向
Oh,come on.
拜託
Ross,please. I found the magazines.
羅斯，我發現那些雜誌了
And finally,that you were "unable to consummate the marriage."
還有你無法履行夫妻間的義務
Well, that makes sense since you're gay and addicted to heroin.
這也難怪，你是同志 又上癮海洛因
You know, I'm sorry, this is insane.
很抱歉，這太誇張了
I'm not addicted to heroin, I'm not gay and there is no problem...
我沒有上癮海洛因 我不是同志
with my ability to consummate anything.
我履行什麼都沒問題
I'll consummate this marriage right here, right now!
我現在就可以在這裡履行
That won't be necessary.
沒有這個必要
And when we were dating, we consummated like bunnies.
我們交往時簡直跟兔子有得拼
If you were involved in a serious relationship, that creates a problem.
如果你們曾經認真交往 那就有問題了
Rest assured, that relationship ended two years ago.
大人，我們2年前就分手了
Strike "consummated like bunnies" from the record.
可以刪掉「跟兔子有得拼」嗎
Is there anything in this record that is actually true?
這份申請書有任何實言嗎？
Well, yes. We got married in Vegas.
有，我們確實在賭城結婚
And the names,I think.
名字應該也沒錯
That's not the way the legal system works.
這樣不符合法律程序
This process is based on an objective review of the facts, not of the lies.
申請註銷得根據客觀事實 而不是謊言
Objection!
抗議
-It doesn't work like that either. -Overruled.
這樣也不合程序 駁回
Oh,stop it.
別鬧了
Based on what I've heard, you certainly don't qualify for an annulment.
從剛才的話聽來 兩位不符合註銷資格
If you don't wanna be together, file for divorce.
如果你們不想在一起 就必須辦理離婚
That's great. You happy? Look what you did with your funny, funny form.
太好了，你高興了嗎？ 都是你的搞笑表格害的
What? Me? What about you and your "consummated like bunnies" nonsense?
我？你那句跟兔子有得拼呢？
What are you typing that for? She said we don't get the annulment.
那…你打什麼打？ 你聽到沒？我們不能辦註銷了
Don't type that. What..
不要打
Stop typing!
別再打了
"Stop typing, stop typing!"
別打了！別打了
Okay, do you see what you're keeping me married to?
你看你讓我嫁的是什麼人？
Get out of my chambers.
請兩位離開我的辦公室
Lady, here's the deal.
好，你給我聽著
I came here for an annulment and I'm not leaving here until I get one!
我是來辦註銷的 沒辦成我絕對不走
-Would you like a night in jail? -Thank you for your time.
你們想在牢裡過夜嗎？ 耽誤您了
That Porsche guy took his car back.
保時捷的主人把車開走了
But you found the keys to his clothes?
但你檢到他的衣櫥鑰匙？
No, I just love the way it feels when everybody thinks I own a Porsche.
不是，我只是喜歡 大家以為我有保時捷的感覺
They'll think you own one because of the clothes?
你穿這樣別人就會以為你有？
Of course.
那當然
Only an idiot would wear this stuff if he didn't have the car.
白癡才會沒車還穿成這樣
That is true.
那倒是
Yeah,but only a genius would swallow a sonic blaster gun.
不過只有天才 才會誤食音波死光槍
Oh,I've been there.
我也誤食過
I am gonna go drive my Porsche.
我要去開我的保時捷了
You know you don't actually have one.
喬伊，你知道你沒有保時捷吧
What are you doing? I'm in character. Will you talk to her?
拜託，你搞什麼？ 我正在入戲，你說說她，好嗎
I think it just moved. It's poking me.
它動了，現在真的好刺
We'll go to the emergency room.
夠了，我們去掛急診
No, you can't leave me here with them. We're babysitting.
什麼？你們不能把我扔給他們 我們正在帶孩子
The babies are asleep. You'll be okay on your own.
寶寶都睡了 你撐一下一定沒問題
You can't leave me with them. We're a team.
但你們不能把我扔給他們 我們是一隊的
We're playing a zone. They'll triple-team me!
在打區域聯防 他們會以三打一
He's got plastic in his throat. We gotta go to the hospital.
他的喉嚨卡了個塑膠玩具 我們非去醫院不可
But a doctor won't be able to help him. And it's just gonna...
但醫生也幫不了他
naturally pass through his system in seven years.
反正過個7年就會自動排出
-I think that's gum. -I'm pretty sure it's gun.
那是口香糖 我確定是死光槍
This really hurts. Let's go.
真的很痛，我們走吧
But no! A real man wouldn't just run to the hospital.
男子漢才不會衝去醫院
No! What would Krog do?
克洛格會怎麼做？
Why isn't that valet back with my Porsche?
泊車小弟怎麼還沒 把我的保時捷開來？
Maybe because you've got the keys?
因為鑰匙在你手上嗎？
保時捷
-That was totally your fault. -My fault? You threatened the judge.
都是你的錯 我的錯？你威脅法官
You ripped the paper out of the court reporter's machine!
你把書記員的打字紙撕下來
That was the only way I could get him to stop typing!
那樣才能阻止他打下去
Hi. How are the Gellers?
蓋勒夫婦好嗎？
Don't call us that.
不准那樣叫我們
The judge wouldn't let us get an annulment. Now we gotta get a divorce!
法官不准我們辦註銷 我們得去辦離婚
Did a Porsche throw up on you?
你被保捷附身了嗎？
It's "Porsche-a"!
是保時捷
Me taking care of you is no problem, huh?
我完全可以照顧你們對吧？
You guys feel safe, right?
你們覺得很安心吧？
I'm gonna take that spit bubble as a "Yeah,I do!"
吐泡泡就表示「安心」
Let's get rid of this dirty diaper. I'll set you up with a clean one.
我扔了髒尿布 就幫你換一塊乾淨的
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you. I just have to clean that up.
抱歉，我不是故意的 我得先清理一下
Because, let's face it, we're at Monica's.
這是摩妮卡的家
I broke it. All right. Well, that's just the way things go.
破了，反正東西遲早都會壞
Okay. Good.
好，就這樣
Why are there only two of you?
為什麼只剩兩個？
Where's Leslie?
萊絲莉呢？
Well, you can't answer. Leslie? Where are you, Leslie?
你們不會說話 萊絲莉？你在哪裡？
Now would be a good time for your first words.
萊絲莉 現在是開口說話的好時機
Well, look at you!
你看看你
You are a little bit mischievous. My gosh!
你有點皮喔，真是的
Oh, you're a lot mischievous.
是非常皮
Well, it'll dry.
反正會幹
You sit with your brother and sister now...
去跟哥哥妹妹躺在一起…
who aren't there.
他們不在
How do you feel?
你還好嗎？
Let's just say Krog will be equipped to destroy the universe again...
克洛格就又能毀滅宇宙了
in 12 to 14 hours.
再過12到14小時
I totally took care of the babies all by myself.
我一個人把孩子都帶好了
I fed them,bathed them and put them to bed.
餵奶、洗澡、哄他們睡覺
And protected them from a tornado?
還保護他們躲過龍捲風？
Oh,my God!
我的天哪
I know. The babies are asleep.
對啊，寶寶都睡了
Phoebe, what happened here?
菲比，家裡是怎麼了？
I did it. I took care of the babies all by myself.
我做到了，我一個人照顧寶寶
-But my apartment! -Was the setting of Phoebe's triumph.
但是我的房子 是菲比勝利的戰場
But the mess!
但是這一團亂
Is not as important as the fact that Phoebe took care of the babies.
比起菲比的辛勞實在不算什麼
You're right. I shouldn't freak out.
你說得對，我不該大驚小怪
This is what it'll be like when we have babies. When's that?
等我們有了孩子也會這樣 那是什麼時候呢？
Phoebe, look at this mess!
菲比，你看你弄得多亂
Oh,honey. Thank God you're home. I was getting worried.
親愛的，你總算回來了 我都開始擔心了
I picked up the divorce papers.
我去領了離婚證書
I've already signed everything. I put little X's where you need to sign.
該簽的我都簽了 你要簽的地方我也畫了叉
Little X's. Great! That makes up for everything.
畫叉，真好 這樣就前嫌盡釋了
You know, you've done a lot of stupid stuff too, okay?
我…你也幹過很多蠢事好嗎
Name one stupid thing that is as stupid as this one.
有哪一件跟這次一樣蠢
How about you flew to London to stop my wedding?
你飛去倫敦阻止我結婚怎麼說
You told me you loved me after I was married.
我已經結婚了，你還說你愛我
Wait,that was different. I did those things because I was in love with you.
慢著，那不一樣 我做那些事是因為我愛你
Right.
正是
You're right. That's very different.
你說得對，的確很不一樣
So let's just sign the papers.
總之趕快簽一簽吧
What?
怎樣？
Nothing.
沒事
Okay, can we just sign, please?
請簽名
Congratulations.
恭喜你
Okay, wait,Ross. Wait a minute.
羅斯，等一下
I kind of have a little confession.
我有件事要坦白
What?
什麼事？
Well, you know, this whole marriage thing.
結婚這件事
Kind of my idea.
算是我的主意
Excuse me?
什麼？
Remember how we were too drunk to remember anything when we were married?
當時我們不是醉到什麼都想不起來
Yeah？
怎樣？
I didn't really wanna say anything, but it just kept coming back to me.
我很不想說 但是我的記憶一直回來
We were in the casino and you thought it'd be funny to eat a lot of grapes.
記不記得我們在賭場 你突然覺得狂吃葡萄會很好玩
And I thought it would be funnier if we got married.
然後我覺得我們結婚會更好玩
So as a compromise we decided first to get married and then...
於是我們折衷，先去結婚
to eat a lot of grapes.
再去吃很多葡萄
Sorry I got us into this whole thing.
抱歉惹出這些麻煩
So then if you think about it...
所以仔細想想
this is all your fault.
這一切都是你的錯
Yeah, don't push it, though.
不要得寸進尺
I gotta say...
我知道...
I know I divorce a lot of women.
我跟很多人離過婚
Never thought I'd be divorcing you.
卻從來沒想過會跟你離婚
I know.
是啊
I always thought if we got married, that'd be the one that stuck.
我總覺得要是我們結婚 一定會天長地久
And it wouldn't be a secret...
不會是秘密結婚
and we wouldn't have our wedding dinner at Pizza Hut.
也不會在必勝客吃酒席
Did I even treat?
我有請客嗎？
No, it was on the house. It was a newlywed special.
沒有，那是免費的 新婚夫婦特惠
That may be the most depressing thing I've heard.
我沒聽過這麼令人沮喪的事
I should get these to my lawyer's office.
我去律師那裡送件
Thanks for taking care of all this.
謝謝你把事情都辦妥
No problem.
不客氣
-I'm gonna need a copy of those. -Totally.
我要一份副本 沒問題
Careful around my Porsche!
別在我的保時捷旁邊亂跑
Hi,Joey.
喬伊
Hey. How you doing?
你們好嗎？
He has the most amazing Porsche under there.
他有一輛最拉風的保時捷
I'd show you,but I just tucked her in. She's sleeping.
我很想給你們看 但我剛哄到她睡著
Would you like to go for a drink?
要不要去喝杯酒？